Hello friends,
welcome to the brothel once again. In today's
video, we'll show you how
you can check your ICICI
Life Insurance policy status from the comfort of your home.
Friends, with this video,
we'll not only teach you how to make a promise day for your policy, but also
explain how to add it to your policy document if
your contact details have changed, if
your mobile number has changed, or if
your address has changed.
Here, we'll not only
check your policy details, but there are also
many services related to your policy,
for which we have to constantly
call the agent. If you
watch this video carefully,
you can add all these tasks yourself. So, friends,
at the end of the video, if you found this video
helpful, do
n't forget to press the like and subscribe button. This lets the
YouTube algorithm know that this is
used oil content, and when other people
search for it, it
appears at the top within half an hour. This is
beneficial for you in one way because the more you search for it, the better.
We will help you optimize your YouTube search. The
next time
you search, you will see elements containing these subsets.
Friends, first of all
you will have to go to ICICI Pru
live.com. I have given its link
in the description and also in the comments. As soon as you go there,
a page like this will appear.
You will see in the top right corner you will see something
like Login. You have to
click there. Such an option will
open in front of you where you will see the options of Customers,
Individual, Corporate, Non-Individual,
Rescuers. If you
know that you are an individual customer,
then you will click on Individual and then
your login page will open. Here
you basically have to enter your mobile number, email
ID in the first column and
enter the password in the second column. There are
many of us who do
not remember these media passwords. For them, the
simplest thing is to go down and
select the option of Login via OTP. I have
selected this option. As soon as you select this option,
another page opens
where you can  If you want, you
can get your OTP in your email or mobile number.
This is good for those people who are on
our lines and do not have a mobile network to
receive their OTP. So choose the email option. For the
rest of the people, enter your mobile number here
and press the submit button.
In some time, you will get a notification of your OTP
that Patiala and Tips have been sent to your
registered email ID and mobile number.
For this, you will have to
press the send OTP button and as soon as
you press it,
you will enter the OTP that comes there and your
notice will be successful.
After logging in, a page like this will appear where the
registered mobile number, email address, all these
things will be displayed, all the ones with
quit and the real ones. If
you want to verify that all this is
correct, then you will press the confirm button.
If you feel that your
registered mobile number or alternate
mobile number has changed, then you
can change it there by pressing the edit button.
Next, we come as soon as you see such a
dash  When you come to the board, you will see the
policy related details here in a very short form
and this is the problem of everyone
that how do we check it completely. You do
n't have to do anything, you have to press the
3 lines in the left hand corner above,
when you press that line,
this kind of option will be opened in
front of you where
you will see all these options from dashboard to sitemap.
As soon as you
click on policy details, you will be
able to know the complete details related to your policy, how much is your premium amount,
next you will get to pay the premium,
what is your mode of payment,
you will get to see all these details here.
Next, go to my profile. With the
help of my profile, you can see
what things you have mentioned about yourself in this policy
and this kind of
paste will be visible where you will see date of birth,
first name, last name, email, message to
status, all these things. There are
many things in it which you cannot change,
like your name has become Mogya in the last,
but if marital status is  Or
your PAN number or mobile number,
you can easily change all these things by pressing the edit button here.
Next, we come to the
transaction options in the quadruple option in the left corner of this dashboard.
You can see the transaction option - Premium Top
Switch, Premium Redirection, Change in
Portfolio.
All these options are transaction related options. By pressing this premium button from this transaction related option,
you
can also pay your premium online if you want. In this,
for particulars, some of our friends who
want to cancel the policy,
if they are not able to know the surrender value
or if we are not helping them
in surrendering the policy, then they
can see the mark here. The surrender option is
given in it. You
can surrender your policy by pressing it. Fund value is
important for those who
follow the policy. They know that
their current fund value keeps changing. So
if they want to know
their fund value every day, then they can
check it by pressing the fund value here.
Next we come to the statement, here
you deposit the tax premium, if
you want tax rebate then you will get it
in the tax certificate, if you want any such
document then you can download it from here,
here you will get the policy unit
statement, it will be available in the policy document,
if any of our friends have
their policy document ready then they
can download it by clicking here,
apart from this, whether it is premium receipt or
portfolio statement,
you do not need to wander anywhere else for all these things, all these
things are available in your mobile today,
friends, if you found the
things mentioned in the video useful then
like the video and definitely press the subscribe button,
thank you very much to all of you for staying connected with us in this video.